hello
my name is green
can you can you hear me
welcome back to another episode of
hermitcraft
these machines are too
loud
as you can see
i've made the world's noisiest farms
powering my new hippie
machine and this is oh this is making me
lag as well
and there's impulse over there hold on
i'm gonna see what they're up to
[Applause]
oh my goodness these machines are so
loud i can't even hear the rockets i was
just inviting you guys over
to come see this redstone project that
you guys hired me for you have no idea
how good it is to hear
again that
this is
what have i created oh man i can hear
that all the way from over here dudes
it's yeah it's not it's
nasty you've made your
countdown clock awesome
yeah yep it's up and running it is ready
to go that is um that is a flying box of
not very hippie like but then i can't
really talk either
yeah i don't know what you two have been
up to you know i'm building giant
shrooms and you guys are making
industrial machines i mean
conflict of interest here gentlemen
don't worry by the time i'm done it'll
all be hidden okay impulse can you come
and can you go and show us the clock i
want to take sure see how it works
take the sucker for a spin it's pretty
cool it's got some different things it
can do it can go up see three two uh
four it should go there we go it can go
back down
this is the kind of thing that sounds
really easy in minecraft but it's just
it's not
yeah i wanna take a look at this
redstone no it is it is crazy my head is
still spinning from this redstone i was
going cross-eyed and of course
of course along the way there was
missing components that i had to find
after the fact and there's always of
course i don't really know what's going
on there but
yeah
well we've definitely hired the right
man for the job you can just conclude
that this is voodoo witchcraft can i
press one of the buttons i want to press
the button you can't that's what i was
doing i was trying to see if it was
green proof but i think i proved that
it's not
decrease
so there we go the signs are there also
i just want to let you guys know i've
been i've been trying to think you know
as a hippie as i now am and all of the
parts used were organic they're all
organized oh organic redstone yeah
it took me a little extra time to make
sure that they were all organic to
gather that all up but yeah i made sure
to do that so it's all fitting yes this
is brilliant so now that this is done
that means we can initiate the countdown
to the giant rv surprise oh man so uh
impulse if you would if you would do me
a favor and set it to three days time
whoa
three days three days
whoa it's going that soon huh this thing
is launching in three days
wow okay there's one one
two
and there should be three unless i did
the redstone rock three there we go all
right it's beautiful
we're gonna count this down and it's
gonna be glorious
oh man i'm getting kind of nervous
countdowns make me nervous gentlemen
that's the whole point it's freaking me
out we could have just put a sign by
area 77 saying three two one but this
this says it all right this says it yeah
the only thing to do is to cover it up
and then watch the area 77 guys squirm
has it started has it like has it
started this is it yeah this is it three
days remaining oh my goodness okay this
is this this is okay
whoa
this is getting exciting it'll be all
right dude we'll manage
now that the countdown's done i really
need to get a move on with this because
i've not really explained this very well
but this machine
is directly related
to the rv launch and big prank
distraction and i need to get this
finished as soon as possible because
without all of these
it isn't going anywhere but let me
quickly show you what i've done i've got
the bamboo farm and i got the cactus
farm you already all know all that but i
added oh the noise no
there we go
so i've added an xp volt all of all this
is doing is sending cactus down here
it's burning with the bamboo so cactus
feeds one the bamboo feeds the bottom
there we go and then this is filling up
with green dye eventually this will
store so much xp that i can just
mend anything that i need so that's a
byproduct but
any cactus that isn't used it goes
flying straight into here and is
producing bone meal which is one of the
big things that i'm going to be needing
so right i think i just need to put my
head to the grindstone
finish this project it's nearly there i
kind of understand what's going on
let's just get it done because otherwise
without this
that isn't going anywhere let's begin so
i followed another redstone tutorial
from ill mango in order to make this
particular farm now before you all go
commenting saying i'm in the wrong biome
i already know i'm in the wrong biome
but it's not a big deal for what i want
to do with it so don't worry about it
this machine is my big
first redstone project and i've just
been really excited to work on it so
watch out season seven because redstone
green's gonna be hitting hard oh my
goodness doesn't this look really
impressive okay maybe not super like i
should have not used cobblestone but hey
this is my first proper redstone project
it's not really finished
but i'm not gonna lie
i could use some help
so i've created this flower farm and
let's pop it on to see how it works
it's um
it's a lag machine for sure oh i haven't
got any uh boatmeal in it let me just
pop that in there we go now it's gonna
work so this is gonna produce a lot of
flowers and seeds you can see them all
there and then they magic their way up
and then they end up in the water stream
blah blah blah blah it's a big fancy
machine and it's awesome however this is
the bit i'm struggling with i've got a
couple of filters set up and then i am
catching all of the flowers but
it's not going so well the filter this
filter doesn't work particularly well
there's maybe too many items
look at it
it's also quite hard to watch with all
this lag going on this is not a machine
that can be on for very long so what i
actually need
is impulse to help me out so i've
planned it all out you can see
that from a distance i've got the
outline of a barn this is going to be my
lag barn
because all of these machines are gonna
well it's gonna make the computer chug a
little bit so we've got our flower farm
our sugarcane farm cactus and bamboo and
they will all work together to produce
multiple things and i want all of those
things to end up here and be accessible
so you get green dye sugarcane bone meal
yellow flour red flowers oxidize you
know all the flowers and stuff and i
know that i'm not in the best biome for
this but it honestly doesn't matter too
much i can just craft them all up and i
want to be able to turn them all on and
off from here like like this
so
there's still actually quite a lot to do
here
but i don't know what i'm doing so what
i need to do is ask
some help but i want to know what this
looks and feels like to maybe even
sounds like if i turn on all of the
machine
all right that's the sugarcane one on
now let's turn the bamboo on boop
and now the cactus
there's a lot of moving parts here look
at it go that is the
well i can't actually hear it if i go in
here can you hear it yeah that's the
noise of progress and
production
it's actually not laggy at all
like okay maybe it's it's a little bit
frame rate drops but
overall
this has gone really well this thing
gets through so much bone meal though
it's not gonna be able to keep up so
let's turn all of these off following
the tutorial was the easy part
i've started linking them up but there's
still a long way to go so let's hop over
to impulse's little rv and give him
a little instruction i'm probably
there's probably too much to to tell him
all in one go i'll just pop it on here
shall i okay so i've written impulse i
need some more redstone help it's kind
of too long for signs so i will just
give you the details on discord i will
also help decorate the countdown for you
thanks g
so that countdown is some sort of
technical marvel i don't know how it
works big mystery box and it actually
says two now it's it's the next day
and the countdown is already at two days
two days
oh boy
stressing me out a little bit and i know
what happens it's gonna be really fun to
see how people react to that
and i also noticed while i was here
there's a little payment there's some
diamonds and paid in full by b double o
uh thank you for your generous gift it's
not really a gift is it because you
bought it my love is purchased very
easily you shall have it forever
not really a gift b-dubs but um thank
you for paying as i need some of these
diamonds as there's been quite a lot
that needs doing underground
and if we hop down into the toilet flush
i can show you that cleo has actually
done her part of the project which is
really cool going here she's made an
awesome looking armor stand thing of us
playing chess
this is so cool this is exactly what i
wanted to bamboozle the guys over at
area 77 now i only gave her 20 diamonds
so i'm actually going to give her a full
stack of diamonds extra for this because
it's just so cool so i'm gonna head over
and do that but first i need to meet up
with rendog about making this tunnel a
reality i need to make this tunnel here
a reality and start heading into area
77.
we got a lot to do let's go
what are you doing
well you've asked me to help you dig a
hole so i'm i'm here i'm ready to go
yeah but you you know that doesn't move
right
well yeah i've been looking for the on
button
i've actually been digging uh not
sitting inside there pretending to be
digging i've actually been digging um a
big hole
and
yeah do you want to do you want to see
because i actually i really need some
help now it's um quite a long
tunnel and it's it's at the point now
where it needs to spread out something's
happened to your hole though man
i tried to fight nature and nature one i
think is the best way i could describe
the situation here i thought i when i
completed this i was like yes i have
conquered the grass i came in here again
and uh
yes dude there's no there's no winning
there is lit there's no point fighting
this at all
well listen i got two pickaxes i'm ready
to go
ready to diggy diggy hole so is it
through here is this is this where we're
going yep all right so we're gonna go in
now area 77 is over here this is the
line yeah i've i went in the upstairs
and like the coordinates and this is the
exact point
across the boundary area 77 okay hippie
land area 77
land
right okay let's let's open the mine
carts and let's go down right to the end
of the tunnel because it's it's actually
a really big area doc and scar didn't
mess around oh wow
i mean you haven't messed around either
this is quite the impressive little
tunnel that you've done so far man
build a tunnel you've got to do it
properly right oh you got the map up
also okay yeah this is why i need your
help because okay if we actually take
this map here you can see where we are
in the bottom right hand corner
um and okay we're at the point now where
we might want to like turn right and go
forward and we want basically we want to
spread out into multiple locations here
let me throw you the map and you can see
let's have a quick squish
oh you can actually see yes we need to
go this way to head toward the
sheepshead farm i mean we don't know
where the machine is right so we've got
yeah we've got a tunnel under each of
these different
things i would think exactly but these
maps are brilliant like i didn't
actually expect it to show exactly where
you are i know we can tell and we can
make a huge tunnel system and make sure
we hit all of these different uh points
to look for all the stuff they've got
hidden and we definitely
only paid nine beat routes for them so
what a steal um yeah listen i've brought
us some music here too dude because this
is going to be a lot of digging i think
so i brought the boombox ready to go um
do you have any records that you
particularly want to play i mean i've
got a selection i'll just uh
we've got a long way to go this
direction
now i don't want to challenge rendog's
choice in music but this was a
particularly strange choice of track
i don't know if he's a hippie or if he
just wants to move to russia now
very strange ren but it kind of works
with this time lapse so what we're doing
is we are properly tunneling under area
77 but you cannot tell them you cannot
tell doc or scar what we're doing this
is a really top secret project and we
spent a long time making these tunnels
look pretty so we don't want them ruined
thanks you've got to keep this top
secret
[Music]
we did a lot of digging today wren has
made it all the way down there and i
have made a tunnel all the way down
there as you saw so it looks a little
something like this it starts over here
and it makes its way all the way along
to about
about here and then it branches out and
rens is going this way and then mine is
going like a right angle here to the
watchtower and then hopefully over to
the hangar and then when we break
through we can take a little look around
and see if the time machine is there
that's what we're after however
there's too much digging for one day so
let's head back because there's actually
a bunch of other things that i need to
do today that uh isn't just building a
hole or building a machine man i've got
i've got a lot to do recently it's been
hard to get all of these things in
anyway
so let's get out of here and head back
over
what
what is that
has has impulse made some sort of noise
machine that sounded like a bunch of
notebooks being sent over and over again
something's going on how do you activate
is it just on a timer i think it just
activates on its own this is really bad
i don't know where it is but it's it's
actually quite an up well there's my
tunnel
this stupid noise machine
wait
is it in here oh my goodness where is
this noise machine oh they they could
have very easily have found this if
this is not very well hidden okay this
this is driving me mad
where is it this can't be impulsed and
make this
there's no way
this is one of them area 77 contraptions
this is the
this is exactly the sort of thing doc
would do
but i'm not sure why i feel like i'm
getting close is it in the tree i
legitimately cannot find this thing
it sounds like it's inside the trees but
i can't find it also can i point out
just for a second
that
area 77 have made a gigantic wall
all the way around
their base
but what i want to know is did they
realize
that you can walk through it at every
single point
i mean it looks awesome but
i don't i don't think i don't think
they've like tested this out
[Laughter]
still
i wouldn't want to go in there just
what the heck
they got like a is that a tie fighter
from the house
oh and their dudes have gone from the
truck that was watching us
what on earth are they up to
well
we're gonna find out soon because
there's only two days to go right
forget the noise machine i can't find it
i'll have to leave it up to impulse or
rent have a go i i did spend a good 10
to 20 minutes looking for it and it's i
don't understand i honestly don't
understand where it's gone so the next
thing on our list is to check if we have
sold any more saharan now memberships
because we need to go and put our
diamonds holy moly we sold two more
that means i have now sold four
memberships in total 400 diamonds going
in the pot because we need to head back
to sahara right now to deposit all of
these to see who's going to win i have
no idea how much iskow has sold i have
no idea how much mumbo has sold but
four seems like a pretty good amount
okay here we are why am i on the middle
one why is mumbo on the beat
well mumbo has sold zero
oh dear
iska has sold four as well
oh no
okay
well i have also sold for
so that is 400 diamonds i need to sell
one more if i'm gonna poor mumbo
poor mumbo he's he's got the biggest
stack on the sahara rung
and he hasn't sold any yet
maybe i'll buy one from you mumbo i i'll
be a true pal okay
but yeah it looks like i'm neck and neck
at the moment this is awesome we've sold
eight memberships in total oh you've
actually labeled them you sold one to
jelly jelly is a cat iskal
that's not a hermit so scar bought two
stress and b double o
i
don't know who bought mine
i'll be honest i have no idea who bought
mine
so it looks like we'll probably have to
target a couple of people that don't
have the memberships now the other thing
that i desperately need to do
is to add a few more boxes to sahara now
there is oh that's actually not a bad
box but i guess people don't need it
that is an awesome box as well i don't
know why no one has bought that
okay so there's only two boxes left
that's it right so we need to fix that
by
adding our own shulker boxes
fortunately we have a lot of spare
shulker boxes in our storage room so i'm
going to make up a good few boxes to try
and store some things in because it
would suck if we got lots and lots of
memberships for our new shop
but then there was nothing to sell
and i've also got a bunch of gravel left
over from when i gathered all of that so
i will put one of those in right give me
a minute i'm gonna put together some
fresh box deals to go in there oh
string
we can sell that
let's head over to the mess that is my
base actually while we're out here let's
head over to cleo's base
and give her some more diamonds for the
awesome job she did on those armor
stands won't take a second so i've added
a little note saying mission success
nice job looks amazing have some more
diamonds g so i'm gonna give her a full
stack of diamonds
i feel like that is more than fair i
wouldn't be able to make those armor
stands and
she did such a cool job on it anyway
let's go back and sort out the sahara
now deals
every time i come back here i think to
myself i really need to sort this out
well this is a good way to get rid of
some clutter
let's see if we can put together five
boxes plus the gravel one all right i'm
gonna need like
20 minutes to do this
so i went to go and fill up a shulker
box full of sand and do you remember my
infinity room well this is actually the
setting for the map it's completely made
of snow this is what gives the infinity
room its complete blankness this whole
big sheet but i just hit the jackpot and
i found
three
chests full
of sand
that i forgot existed
this must have been dug out at the start
of the episode or very close to the
start of the series
and it's just been sitting here
how on earth have i missed this
well this is just free sand i have got
all the sand that i need and
this will fill up my very last
now deal okay i've done way more than
five sahara box deals now i know that
we've sold eight memberships so i wanted
to put in a
not exactly a wide variety but some good
deals in here so let me show you what
i've got
one full shulker box of tnt i have no
idea how much i've been charged for that
a box of string a box of gravel
a box of logs and chest this is
incredibly
valuable
so that's a really good deal some
rockets some sponge i don't know if
people really need sponge at this point
but it's there
sand
and more sand i don't think it gets much
better than that so i think that's where
i am going to stop my deals and i just
need to price these up and we are good
to add them to the system the tnt is
going to be 15 diamonds and that is
because it costs so much sand per tnt
this is like
four boxes full of sand plus all of this
gunpowder plus the shulker box itself
whoa that kind of scared me
string a box full is four diamonds
a box full of gravel is
four sand is four diamonds like i said i
really want these to be worth a lot so
that's why i'm going for such
ridiculously low prices i really want
the now membership to be worth it
but then some things don't make sense
like this one's gonna be shiny sand
which is five diamonds so
you know
sponge
to be honest most of these that are four
or five diamonds are
cheaper than buying just normal shulker
boxes so i mean i don't know why you
wouldn't do it
the one that's full of logs i'm gonna
sell for 15 diamonds now you might think
that's quite expensive for now but it's
not let's say that the shulker box is
only two diamonds two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen fifteen so the rest
all of these
are for free so this is about half price
what you would normally pay if you
needed all of these logs
and let's not forget how expensive
chests can be and you do get through
these in build so i think 15 diamonds is
pretty fair for that so that is all of
my deals i now need to go and add them
i really also need mumbo and iskal to
contribute plenty of boxes as well
because
i'm gonna very quickly go through all of
my stock all right there we go one two
three four five six seven
eight
it should start filling up i hope
it's doing something it's tick if it's
burning my stuff i'm gonna cry
there we go my deals have come up lots
of logs for 15 diamonds that's a really
really good deal i like i've only put
stuff in here that i think i would buy
as well like
this one for example lots of sand five
dive it's a no-brainer really it's a
no-brainer
and every time you get to keep the
shulker box maybe the tnt one is too
expensive i don't know let's see i don't
even think anyone needs that much tnt
it's a ridiculous amount i know i didn't
that's why i'm selling it
alright well that is now my chores done
for the day
it's been a busy episode but guess what
the grind doesn't end here for me but it
is the end of the episode so i will see
you in the next one where the countdown
clock will officially hit zero
and well you'll have to find out in the
next episode good bye
[Music]
ow